I did it I did
it I turned the 100 into the mill nobody
believed in me where I did it
$91,000
$200,000
$332,400 th000 in profit so we be at
$600,000
$824,000 smackaroos boys bro three
[__] months turning $100 into $1
million I'll never forget the day after
my birthday as I'm celebrating it I'm
like well why should I be celebrating my
birthday if I don't feel like I've
achieved one of the biggest things that
I've been wanting to achieve that's
turning $100 into a million I failed
three four five times in front of
hundreds of thousands of people which is
humiliating we're officially be the
account we about to hit margin car right
now and uh I kind of took a break from
social media I I it cracked me I didn't
have what it took to be that Traer to
have that flip even though I had made
multiple seven figures in trading I
simply didn't have the mindset I didn't
have the willing power to push through
all the negativity and push through the
battles that I was going to go through
in this challenge to succeed so a day
after my birthday I said [__] it let's
do it what's the worst that can happen
we fail we do it again and little did I
know the year that I took off the
challenge to become this now stronger
Trader and more built for it was the
time that I was actually going to
achieve it this time my target was to
double the account every single week
meaning we start off with 100 take it
from 100 to 200 200 to 400 400 to 800
800 to 16 and so on and according to my
calculations we should finish the
challenge in about 3 months give or take
depending if we enter a losing streak
and how much we lose in that losing
streak and we're looking for a risk
reward of a 1 to2 meaning if we risk
100% of the account we want to gain 200%
so that way we can actually meet the
double every single week and every
single trade like always I'm going to
share on my Instagram on my telegram on
my Discord on my YouTube everything so
people can go and watch Journey for
themselves and learn from it and see
that it's actually possible and little
did I know that I was about to make
history in the trading industry turning
$100 into a million day trading in under
3 months and this is how it went I'm
going to try and turn these $100 into a
million and we got to hurry up because
the market is officially open 9:45 on
Monday and we already have the account
ready to go so my goal the first week is
to take the $100 into $200 meaning I
risk 100 to make 200 and as I'm actually
going to be identifying the top markets
that I'm going to be trading for the
week I had a curious idea let me go look
back at the previous challenge that I
did to see if the markets that I'm going
to going to be trading for the first
week have some type of connection or
correlation with the first markets that
I traded in the last Challenge on the
first week 11 months ago you can clearly
see this guy right here which by the way
I don't know who this guy is or who he
thinks he is wearing three chains look
at him but you can see right here in the
markets actually so the first two pairs
were actually GBP Cad and GBP USD for
this time around literally a year later
when we're doing the challenge it's
actually the second pair and then the
third pair was actually pretty crazy
this just hyped me the [__] up meaning
that I am on the right path and have a
clear mindset going to execute the
trades that I need to execute in order
to pass this challenge that nothing has
changed in my strategy technical wise
the only thing that has changed is the
trader executing this strategy and a big
difference between this Challenge and
the last one is that I am not going to
let the challenge interfere with my
day-to-day life there's something
different that I want to do with this
challenge is keep a perfect balance not
be cuz I don't want to get drained I
don't want to get burnt out of the
challenge so what I'm going to do is
actually stay in my routine do my
business meetings go to the gym go out
before what I would do I would just stay
up 24/7 throughout the whole week and I
was burnt out the weekends I would just
catch up on sleep and then do it again
in the last Challenge and that's
probably the main reason why I was burnt
out and blew it this time that is not
going to happen I'm going to get
shredded during this challenge cuz it's
also a financial challenge but a
physical challenge because I really do
think that I can get to the best point
I've ever physically been in in my life
last time I looked like a Hermit I was
just stuck in my house not leaving not
going to the gym no social life no
regular day-to-day stuff and I got
blinded I got lost in the journey and I
started just seeing things that I
shouldn't be seeing and like usual every
single Sunday I would pick my top three
top four markets that i' be trading for
the week set my alarms and then be ready
to take the trade either London or New
York session and I think the first pair
I was going to trade was gvp JPY all
right guys good morning it is currently
July 16th Tuesday morning so obviously
stayed up last night it's about like
3:00 in the morning is I stayed up to
catch this trade and it was for no
reason we are currently in the position
and this is literally the max that I can
honestly risk on the account so last
night remember that I explain to you
guys that I was waiting for the market
to have a body closure under this line
right here so we had that body engulfing
Candlestick and then I pretty much
entered on the little quick pull back of
the next one and now that was for no
reason because all of London session as
soon as I fell asleep literally did
nothing but the point is that now price
is pulling back into the area where we
entered usually what should happen is as
soon as we enter the trade it just goes
down with the momentum of the session
but now we haven't but it is what it is
enter the trade s forget my prediction
is that now from here it is going to go
down and as soon as I take the first
position obviously you have to risk 100%
of the account to even get out of that
hole and I remember that I wasn't draw
down as soon as I took the trade I'm
like ah here we go starting off bad and
I think we're were in draw down about 35
bucks right at the start so then there
it's either going to completely blow the
account or Skyrock me out of it so it
can give me the balance that I need to
then take on the next week and follow
the goal that I have for every single
week I got it 1 minute ago positive $15
now we are about to hit Margin Call on
the account 1 minute
later but this trading is so funny dude
oh my God but like always when the trade
went into draw down I wasn't going to
panic I sudden forget because worst case
that can happen I just blow 100 bucks
and I start right again and guess what
happened trade hit take profit ladies
and gentlemen I'm sorry to announce
that we have reached the goal for the
week actively right now we are currently
of
$330 you guys can see here last night
literally what I said happened once
again so look check out GBP JPY right
after that 1 hour bearish engulfing
Candlestick literally the whole momentum
throughout London session was that
bearish move to the downside had my
takeprofit sets at a one to 3.4 risk
reward so meaning if I risked 100 bucks
here then I would made
$340 right here as you guys can see that
is literally the math that is happening
right now Candlestick is going to close
in 15 minutes over here so I want to see
how this Candlestick closes right here
in 15 minutes and then based off of that
I'll then make my decision and let's see
if we can then this week flip this
$450 to then $800 or $900 because that
would put us really really really fast
into the margin that we need to be in
order for us to flip the $100 to the
mail a lot faster it's currently 2:30 in
the afternoon pretty much we close at a
$437 in profit you guys can see here the
my effect book pretty much how it's
looking currently up
$437 these are pretty much the fees we
got to pay these are the orders or
there's nothing open right now this is
the history though you guys can see here
both positions that we ended up taking
that's the profit that we Clos in and
now same [__] gym time know it sucks
that we only get to drive one Supercar
now Lamborghini twin turbo just sold it
wide body ears is at the shop the rear
brake caliper is broken they're fixing
it the Porsche I blew the second gear
here on the Porsche drifting uh
rollsroyce is finally getting done
wrapped should be done today or tomorrow
what other the car do I have the mayb
I'm not going to drive oh yeah oh I sold
the Scat Pack got rid of the Scat Pack
Scat Pack is gone that was probably the
dumbest thing I ever bought yeah the
side by side the side by side is in the
shop as well bro half of my fleet right
now is in the shop I only get to drive a
Ferrari right now we were up 430 bucks I
think and we hit the goal not only for
week one but for week two meaning that I
didn't have to execute a trade next week
or the week after because this one trade
because we said and forget and we caught
a one to three risk to reward we outdid
The Profit that we were even
anticipating for this very same week
just to get started so we were off to a
very good start right at the beginning
so since the week was off to a good
start I pretty much came to the
executive decision that you know what we
hit the goal not only for this week but
for next week we're done for the week
let's not get greedy let's not Chase any
trades let's just set and forget for the
rest of the week and next week will come
back with new Fresh Market new fresh
mindset and then we'll pick up on the
goal which is going to be then taking
$400 to about $900 so then that's
exactly what we did we did not take any
other opportunities and then the next
week we started off fresh with a new
goal and if we were to hit it we're then
ahead 3 weeks in the challenge which is
absolutely beautiful it's week two of me
trying to turn $100 into a million day
trip so like always we started off the
week on Sunday swings analyzing the top
two top three markets that we're going
to be trading for the week and we found
some solid markets where it can probably
even more double the account account is
still on
$437 we got I think seven solid markets
in the markets seven solid markets in
the markets it's a lot of markets it's a
lot of [__] money USD JPY so USD JPY
has a very clean left head kind of right
shoulder action going around here we
broke the neckline now we are retesting
the neckline of The Head and Shoulders
along with the 1H hour EMA 4H hour time
frame looks absolutely phenomenal we're
having a a beautiful 1H hour bearish
engulfing Candlestick looks like we're
having that pullback to retest that
previous structure level and then the
daily time frame does not get any
cleaner than this daily previous
structure level daily EMA and then you
guys can look left it is obviously a
level of resistance whenever we're under
a level resistance whatever we're under
and this line right here what is it you
may be asking around psychological level
157500 or like the smart money concept
guys would call it an order block potato
potato this is a round psychological
level with an area of Interest so this
trade is my number one trade that I'm
going to be interested in taking this
week all I'm really waiting for on this
market so earlier this week what I was
waiting for was this break so that break
already happened and now this pullback
is actively happening so I just got to
wait for price to go back into this area
so I can actually enter this trade we
took the trade which was on USD JPY I
believe
yo up
yo
oh [__] with me huh [__] with me
literally USD JPY as simple and as
effective as I get look at this [__] we
literally had the retest perfectly to
the area of Interest the Maru tweezer
top rejection bearish engulfing
Candlestick I keep telling you you need
an engulfing Candlestick to enter a thow
or a bullish and golfing to enter bu I'm
laughing cuz the mic is moving so the
point is that we're in this trade right
now literally we already at
$550 if this [__] hits that take profit
we'll probably be at like 2 3K it will
probably even break the goal for the
week that we've been anticipate so for
now just going
to S forget but it was taking a little
bit long so I'm not going to sit in
front of the computer all day and
basically do nothing I just exactly what
I said at the beginning of the challenge
I'm going to go play basketball I'm
going to go hit the gym I'm going to go
live my normal life so it doesn't
respect my psychology and I can always
have a fresh mindset when I'm actually
going to execute a trade and I treat the
market it's one thing and then my life
my personal life is a completely other
thing you can either literally make us
or break us it is currently 8:00 p.m.
Miami time so I think it's like about 2
hours or an hour and a half from the
last time I updated you guys and set and
forget now what we're going to go do is
pick up Jordan and for those of you guys
that don't know who Jordan is he's
actually one of my top students where
about 6 years ago he was actually
working at aviation in a place like this
but he wasn't flying the airplanes he
was fixing them he was a mechanic fixing
the planes that were broken down
probably making 50 60k a year and he
didn't want to live that life he wanted
to have a obviously successful life and
because of the set and forget strategy
he managed to not only get out of his
job but make trading his main source of
income in just under two years which is
absolutely legendary and over time we
become really really close friends so
Jordan obviously you know is battling
cancer and stuff and his legs get really
really swollen and have a cold plune so
cold water helps with inflammation we're
going to put him inside the cold plune
in about like 20 30 minutes so we're
going to pick them up now and show you
guys the whole drink all right so this
Jordan we're going to take him out to
the cold plunge it's going to suck bro
it's going to suck it's cold right it's
cold plunge dude it's going to [__]
suck but I'm telling you you're going to
get out you're going to feel [__]
amazing so you know we would pick him up
take him to the cold plunge and then
drop him back off he actually gave me
some Mike Tyson sign gloves which is
super sick because you know Mike Tyson's
a legend I told you I got you in just
came a little late oh
oh
[__] no way signed by the
B for me it's a representation of Jordan
because he's a Fighter fighting through
what he's doing and obviously Mike Tyson
is one of the most legendary Fighters so
it's actually pretty cool to have boxing
gloves signed directly from him all
right guys so trade update we just left
the gym right now trade update is
currently 12:30 in the afternoon so like
I mentioned earlier if that daily
candlestick closes under that previous
structure level we're pretty much going
to set and forget this [__] for a very
long time 4 hours looking good we are
now currently up about $1,200 on the
account so I'm going to continue to set
them forget I think I was already about
like $1,200 1,300 bucks and I had a
decision to make I can either close
there and hit my takeprofit for the week
or I can logically look at the markets
and realize that my analysis and my
strategy is indicating to me that this
trade is going to have a much higher
risk reward ratio so what would I do the
whole reason of me entering a trade is
to capitalize the most I can from the
gains all right guys trade update it is
currently 3 17 in the afternoon and we
are up about 1,600 on the trade and you
guys can see here that the market is
about to close you guys can hear that
the market is about to close in 2 hours
so this daily Candlestick will close
about an hour 42 minutes and it's
honestly going a lot faster than I
anticipated and we're definitely going
to close under that previous structure
level this is why you set and forget
your take profit you never put a take
profit you always put a stop loss to
minimize your losses you never put a
take profit you never want to minimize
your losses so this trade we just
continue to hold and set and forget and
this is where I'm preaching to all of my
students I'm actively monitoring the
markets seeing how much more can we
continue to go in One Direction because
I'm a pro Trend Trader I trade with all
the time frames in my favor so the trade
continues to go in that direction on the
long run you want to trade with the
trend the trend is your friend so in
here is where I continue to set and
forget and analyze the markets and the
trade went from 1,000 in profit to 2,000
currently up about $1,600 on the account
so we're up $22,000 to$ 3,000 God damn
wow bro
wow how long did it take you last year
to do this this is probably almost a
month last year that shows you how much
better of a Trader I've become I'm so
much less attached to the profits and of
the money behind this bro that's crazy
dude and keep in mind goal for the week
was 900 so if I close at this point I'm
ahead by 6 weeks in the challenge
cutting the end goal of turning the 100
into the million to then maybe then two
months so at this point I'm [__]
hyped so then I was we like halfway
through the week I'm basically living my
normal life drifting um going out to the
gym just doing whatever I got to do I
realized that you know what 3K more than
enough I can see the trade that it can
potentially have a reversal because the
structure is starting to shift so I
close my profits there guys see right
here that the account is at officially
$3,000 you guys can see here on my fbook
pretty much uh where we started the
account with the current balance updated
two days ago you guys can see here the
history these are all the trades that we
have taken obviously two trades on GBP
JPY one trade on usdjpy and I did not
take any more trades for the week on
week two because I'm well past the
profit that I need there's no reason on
me to go chase and add new trades so I
simply said and forget and then we
pulled up to the next week where then
the goal is to take 3K to 6K last week
we turned
$437 into $3,000 same thing as always
getting on Sunday swings analyzing the
markets with my students finding the top
two top three markets that I'm going to
be trading with that very week then my
goal is to take 3K to 6K and at this
point in the challenge where I'm at 3K I
no longer have to risk 100% of the
account cuz one I'm already ahead by 4
weeks and my goal once I get to about 3
to 5K is to minimize my risk on the
account to about 50 to 75% meaning if I
take a losing trade I don't start back
at zero at least I still have some
ammunition to then kick back and get
started right where I was for the profit
that I should be for that week so in my
mindset technically yes I did lose some
time but I lost time that I gained not
time that I where I should actually be
in the challenge so for example let's
say I took a loss on the 3K account and
I'm go back to the 900 well it's
technically where I'm supposed to
actually be for the challenge for that
so it gives me the freedom to be able to
actually do that because I'm so ahead in
the challenge all right guys so market
update it is currently
9:49 in the morning we are officially in
the trade so I literally entered let me
before that let me show you guys the
time right so what time is it right now
in Miami I come over here I refreshed
the website 9:49 in the morning so
literally to show you guys we just
entered the trade so look pull up here
so you guys remember how I literally
just mentioned that we were going to
have a pull back into this level to then
sell so we literally had that pull back
perfectly I went exactly to where I I
didn't go exactly to where I anticipated
but got really close I entered it and
just to show you guys proof I was just
recording for Instagram right now as
soon as we enter the trade we're
literally like using margin and [__]
because we enter the trade pretty much
risked everything so I just wanted to
show you guys that but now we're
officially in the trade we are up $400
on it currently right now like always
have to show you guys that it is a real
account so you guys can see right here
that it is indeed a real account you
guys can see where the account is
currently sitting and we're currently
now going to just wait but I explained
to you guys perfectly this I explained
to you guys the break and retest here I
entered at this next retest where we
should have waited for it here should
have waited for the break and retest
here to then sell but then this didn't
happen here but it did happen here we
then entered after the engulfing which
ideally we should be entering up here so
then on week three we started off with a
new trade that we took and we pretty
much went straight into draw down about
50% draw down in the account which is
totally fine I'm okay with it I don't
mind the swings but I continue to set
and forget and then the trade and the
trend ended up going in the favor where
I ended up analyzing and then the trade
actually went back into profit we're
about 5,000 floating in profit keep in
mind my goal for the week is actually
6,000 and like always I'm updating my
telegram Discord Instagram every like
I'm Mass Social Media Blasting these
trades everywhere so I'm not the only
person that's in profit or in loss like
there's hundreds of thousands of Traders
all around the world looking at the same
Market that I am people in Africa people
in London people in the States going
through the same Journey that I'm going
through because if I'm making money
you're making money but if I'm losing
money you're losing money too and I
always have this belief that in order
for you to receive you have to give so
I'm at this point in the challenge where
I need to receive I got to make back
some of these profits I'm like you know
what let me give my boy Sensei a little
gift a m Blanc pen one of 10 in the
world so this is a very special edition
watch so this is a muham mad Ali M Blan
watch so you see it has like Ali through
here and then you see the Muhammad Ali
everywhere throughout here see the
Muhammad Ali everywhere through
here pen was like $3,000 I don't even
think this guy appreciated that [__] but
you know what I don't care because when
I go look at my trade that same night we
were up about $9,000 on the account so
right now we are currently floating
about $6,000 in profit the account is
currently at
$9,000 in equity and you guys can see
this trade right here is literally
continuing the momentum to the downside
just continuing the set and forget Trend
that's why you got to trade with the
trend the trend is your friend so you
guys can see the 4our close very strong
I am going to just continue to hold this
trade uh if tomorrow closes under this
line right here not this one I'm just
copying facing if the Candlestick closes
under this line right there we will
probably turn this into
over
$115,000 easily so let's wait for now
simply just set and forget so if you
want to receive something first you got
to get and I actually put this to test
later throughout the journey and it came
back 10 times more so a little bit more
on that later in the journey and then
the usual happened every single time you
set and forget the trade ended up going
to $5,000 bucking dollars
15,500 so exactly what I was mentioning
to you guys earlier I have to see like
you can't just close a trade right away
right cuz you got to look so obviously
we're going to close a trade because we
wanted it to close under this line or
under this right here and actively looks
like we are piercing through that so
this Candlestick closes in the next 5
minutes as you can see right over here
and if this Candlestick closes under
this line it will mean that it closes
under this structure point
and then there I truly do believe that
it could then easily go from here to
then this point right here so right now
we literally got to wait the next 5
minutes if it closes above like that I'm
going to close it right then and there
if not I'll squeeze it in for the little
bit extra right here just to show you
guys we're up about
15,100 right now [__]
bro Trace set are reversing on me dude
look at this Bro [__] Trace set are
reversing we were up like 15 here and
now
bro like I said forget too much
bro like we Clos the trade like 2 hours
ago so right now it's currently 12:30 in
the afternoon right here you guys can
see where the account is it's officially
closed at
$115,000 you guys can see right here in
the history so you guys can see that we
officially closed this trade at
$122,200 in profit so we closed it
earlier literally as soon as I told you
guys pretty much after it closed that
line so it did make it all the way up to
this structure point and then it had a
reaction so pretty much exactly what I
explained it's going to have a reaction
from that structure point right here and
if we follow this line it's exactly what
it did so our entry points are as
precise as they get our stop losses our
take profit everything with the S fre
strategy [__] sniper yo the goal for
the week was 6 grand we are at
$115,000 so if we were to close at six
grand this week the goal for next week
was to turn 6 to 12 so we just did this
week and next week's goal oh [__] we
should go on a
vacation right ahead of schedule we
should just [__] off for two weeks right
keep in mind I'm looking at the numbers
on the screen because you guys like to
see it I hate looking at the metatrader
and the money go up and down I hate it
it [__] with your mind I only like
looking at the charts because what
happens in the charts directly
correlates with what's happening on the
numbers what happens on the numbers does
not mean that that affects the charts
the charts affects the numbers I only
like looking at the charts because I can
make a logical decision based off of the
price action I can't make a logical
decision based off of me being up 5,000
or 6,000 what connection does that have
to the charts zero so I started
implementing that and educating people
on it and they everybody kind of had
like a oh and AA moment they're like oh
you know what that does make sense I
should only look at the charts and not
the numbers because if you focus on the
structure structure the structure is
going to equal the money this is like
the prime where I was in the challenge
in terms of ahead like I had so much
time ahead of what I anticipated to have
that I felt like the king of the world
at this point so we ended off week three
closing at about $155,000 in profit
where then the goal for next week was to
then take the 15K to then 30k it's week
four of me turning $100 into a Million
last week we were trying to turn $3,000
up to $6,000 now the next week actually
started off kind of slow no trades
towards the beginning of the week so we
kind of just had fun gym drift uh I
think I bought a dope art piece from
Atlanta Atlanta just pulled up so
Atlanta just did a collab with Trump
where he pulled up he actually signed
one of the paintings that he did I
actually have a bunch of Atlanta paint
throughout my whole entire house but I
just got two new posters going to give
one to one of my family members are all
about Trump and I want to put one on the
walk CU I think is a legendary ass
picture and then ARA did it herself
let's go Che it
out oh [__] so this K's in a frame yeah
yeah you got the first two literally the
first two
oh so that's that's basically where he
signed it on the on the original yeah
but this that's my signature oh okay so
yeah but he sign it like somewhere there
exactly yeah okay so oh wait so this is
one out of 47 yeah one and that's two
and then two out of 47 oh [__] so I got
the real oh
[__] appreciate you bro this lit so for
people that don't know I was the first
person that trusted arlanta pain Lambo
yo lamb for real yo the first one it's
crazy he hit me up he was like yo I'm
going to do Art Basel I was at 2020 2022
2022 so y I want I want to paint your
Lambo on Art B and I'm like dog I don't
know a little crazy I'm like you know
what [__] it let's do two Lambo we did
my hood and then Sensei is whole oh yeah
the yeah I remember that mhm then we do
the rose the dawn oh yeah that's right
the Don look I you know I have this
painting oh the Kobe
yeah Dam I haven't seen this one in a
minute yeah yeah Jordan gifted me this
one yeah I remember that but then the
unexpected happened well kind of
expected because I started getting bored
in the challenge I'm so ahead I feel
like Superman I'm winning every trade
I'm ahead by four five weeks I feel like
I can take any trade so the market
wasn't giving me prot Trend trades
meaning having markets to have every
single time frame in the favor to trade
with and there was just nothing
available that checked out everything in
my trading plan I had to do something
togenerate take trades that I shouldn't
be taking all right guys markets update
so I spent the morning kind of just
focusing locking in diving on this trade
to see if I was making the right
decision because we have officially
taken most of the generate trade of the
whole entire [__] challenge the
biggest counter Trend trade it's such a
Degen trade that I did not risk 100% I
risked 20% on this trade so just show
you guys currently market update and we
are negative about $500 cuz we literally
just entered the trade as the
Candlestick just closed right now so
yesterday on Euro USD I'm sure you guys
can remember that I was anticipating for
price to have a sell from this point up
here to then reject and then for price
to actually make it all the way down
here to then have the actual Buy on EUR
USD because we're anticipating for Euro
USD to make it all the way down here
reject this level and then head to the
upside since we broke out we never
retested it so we are expecting for that
retest and here on the 1 hour you can
very very clearly see that we are
creating a potential left head right
shoulder again it's not a confirmed
right shoulder until we don't break
under this neckline but I believe what
it's creating right here it's such a
strong level of accumulation looks like
a 1 hour double top 30 minute time frame
I see it I almost see it like squeezing
into this inwards uh triangle whatever
you want to call this again I hate trend
lines and I hate all this stuff cuz
they're very subjective but you can
literally see how price is squeezing
into this area and I personally believe
it's going to have more of a reason to
burst down than burst up I could be
completely wrong because I don't believe
that this area that is rejecting from
right now is going to be the area to
continue pushing to the upside I think
such a strong move like this has to have
a deeper retracement before actually
heading to the upside so when I go down
to the 4our this 4our Candlestick still
has about 3 hours to close and the last
one closes a very indecisive candle I
think this next one can engulf close
under this which then on the 1 hour
it'll give us the break under this
neckline of The Head and Shoulders if
you notice I put my stop loss a little
bit right above this level because if we
pretty much break Above This the trade
is just going to keep going to the
upside oh that that doesn't seem very
good I'm not good
I mean I called it you know I don't
really care um I'm glad that I ended up
getting that out of my system I'm a
[__] idiot bro like I mean
technically we're still in the trade
right so it could clearly reject this
level right here so it can literally
have the same reaction to the downside
and then this same reaction to the
downside that's why I'm very strategic
with my stop- loss basement but the
trade that I should be taking is at the
break and retest from the neck line of
The Head and Shoulders like I know this
I I know this you know I just decided to
want to get involved but I'm not mad
there's a really set us back much in the
challenge there's an unnecessary loss
well not a loss yet but it's just a
trade update so it's just like an hour
later from the last time that we took
the trade
so yeah now we just got to wait and this
is what a lot of you guys do a lot of
you guys do this a lot of you guys will
take trades that you shouldn't be taking
but you guys won't put the blame on
yourself or hold yourself accountable I
know exactly what I did I did the wrong
thing now do I accept it 100% you guys
when you do the wrong things you don't
accept it you're ready to put the to
blame on on someone's strategy on the
markets on anything but yourself that's
what once you start having that
self-recognition is once you start
developing a nonchalant character for
trading in the markets and that's how
you truly become successful because you
realize that your success whatever the
outcome is successful or not is 100%
because of you not because of another
Outsource like I'm the one that clicked
the sell button the phone didn't click
it just for me you know so for now that
a foret
can't do
this yo that's a sign that we
shouldn't we took the first [__] loss
in the 100 to The Middle
[Music]
[Applause]
come [__] man and um yeah first loss in
the challenge and I said you know what
this loss isn't because of my strategy
my strategy works there was just no
opportunities that week that align with
my strategy I decided to be a slick ass
wanted to be smart and take trades that
I shouldn't because I was bored because
I felt like I was
Superman and this is the week where I
decided to implement a punishment every
single time I break my trading plan I
then have to do something in order so I
hold myself accountable because again
there's hundreds of thousands of people
watching these videos uh following all
the trades making money with me losing
money with me and I don't mind losing
money if I am following my trading plan
but if I'm breaking my trading plan I do
mind losing money because I shouldn't
not be doing that I should only lose
money when I follow my trading plan so
whenever I don't follow my trading plan
there has to be a punishment and that's
where the beetle came in I have owned
Lamborghinis ferari
Porsches
rolls-royces McLaren McLaren bro McLaren
how can I forget about that but this
right here is going to put the biggest
smile on my face the
biggest don't just
yet this right here is my
new
masterpiece
yes
bro perfect
perfect
oh yeah we're getting a haircut on
Thursday night instead of tomorrow we
always get a haircut Friday morning
we're getting one tonight cuz Eric is
not available
[Music]
the [__] is that what do you mean bro
what is that [__] my new
car you don't like it that's fake that's
thing just park up Park
up let me let me explain to you guys the
real moral behind this car right here so
this is so I follow my trading plan and
my trading rules obviously I have a [__]
ton of cool cars but this is going to
Humble me every single time I break my
trading plan this week I have broken my
trading plan twice meaning every single
time I break my trading plan I cannot
drive any of my cars for 24 hours the
only car that I can drive is this for 24
hours so what is that going to
incentivize me to do to not break my
trading plan every single time I break
my trading plan I have to drive this for
24 hours that's just the price and the
consequence that I have to
pay what do you think you [__] with it t
stuff and it's manual it is yes four
it's fourspeed well you going to drift
it that's just
1966 oh sensei's here give me a you
don't like it
no
sorry hey hey hey hey you like
it we're going to be blessed if we get a
[__] whiff of air in
that no air bik oh [__]
oh
[__] all right all right all
right oh we out oh dud it's not that bad
at
all oh this is fantastic
oh y bar has my god oh it has no brakes
that thing is leaning boy is it leaking
no leaning leaning leaning what way like
this really
hey follow your trading plan if not
you're going to be like me oh
[__] oh [__]
[Music]
[__] Beetle and I leave so much by
example that I went to go do some
student podcast with students that have
made over $100,000 with my strategy and
instead of me pulling up in a superar
and taking them for a cool Journey as I
normally do I pulled up in the beetle
even the students were making fun of me
cuz because they expect for me to pull
up and show them the lifestyle and I
show them the real lifestyle I broke my
trading plans and I'm driving this piece
of [__] and I wanted to show it as an
example to them like yeah all right cool
my student made 100,000 but buddy I want
to let you know you need to have
something to hold you accountable how I
am right now because if you don't you're
going to probably end up driving a car
like this so that's why I led by example
and to show the students live in person
that they need to continue to follow the
trading plan to be successful the moment
they don't they're going to end up in a
car like that it's kind of a funny way
to look at it but it's the reality of
the situation this is where the humbling
begins you guys know how much I love
driving my Porche GT3 and driving it
like a man and driving my Ferrari and
driving it like a
man but man's got to do what a man's got
to do and a man's got to pay the price
and I'm doing this show you guys I'm
holding myself accountable for breaking
my
rules and as you guys can tell I've
already attempted to drive this vehicle
and uh
today starts the 24-hour clock where I
will only drive the beetle what name
should we give the beetle keep in mind
it's a 1966 Volkswagen Beetle it has the
original engine four-speed
transmission I tried turning it on
earlier it did not work we're going to
try again right now so this is to show
you guys that I'm going back to my roots
of me literally having to hold myself
accountable when I do something wrong I
don't want to do this but if I don't
follow my tra plan I will no longer be
able to drive a [__] Ferrari or a
Porsche I'm going to probably be driving
some [__] like this so I'm going to keep
following my trading plan so I don't end
up in a [__] car like this please
turn
[Music]
on what name should we give it should it
be a he should it be a her come on come
on
work my way
up watch what do you guys know about
this what profit of Trader knows how to
do this
[Music]
all right yeah we only got space for
two oh
oh yeah let's just push it let's push it
so we ended off on week four with the
first loss that we had in the whole
entire challenge so this was a big
uppercut to my ego because at to this
point I felt invisible I literally felt
like I could do anything I could win
every single trade it's week five of me
trying to turn $100 into a million day
trading last week we ended up taking two
unnecessary losses because I broke my
trading plan so we started off the
challenge with about 8,000 which is
where we left off last week because cuz
we took the account from 15 to 8,000 so
at this point in the challenge I am not
scared to execute a position I'm being a
little bit more selective so I actually
avoided some wins that I could have
taken but I also avoided a couple of
losses that I could have taken and funny
enough because some of my friends were
actually calling me in the middle of the
week saying hey you going to get enter
this and enter this I'm like no dude
trust me I'm not going to enter these
counter Trend trades I don't want to
drive the [__] Beetle my God what the
[__] oh wow just saw this right now so
nzdusd I'm actually laughing because one
of my friends called me earlier he's
like yo what should I do with nzdusd I
entered earlier this week Sunday night
when you sent it out on Sunday studing
this one of my friends that I went to
high school with literally one of the
only close friends that I have outside
of you know my my team and he told me
he's like yo should I close nzdusd or do
I hold I'm like dude if you hold it can
have the risk of having a pool back I
don't think you should hold I think you
should close he's like nah no no no I'm
going to set him forget I'm like brother
you have to know when to set him forget
and when to not set him forget this is
not the time you don't want to like not
close this trade and I'm laughing cuz I
know he is I know I'm going call him I'm
going call him yes so I'm not friend
I'll call you a 100 times I don't give a
[__] yo yo you're
sleeping to have you seen your trade
yeah [__]
you
bro [__] me I told you bro you tell me
to have a pullback not a whole [__]
move straight
down that's what I told you bro I told
you I was going to have a pullback bro
you don't [__] listen to me dog what
are you think D you told me S forget no
no no no no no no no no I told you don't
set him forget this trade it's going to
have a pullback you didn't listen to me
bro Y no no I literally told you bro I'm
like yo it's going to it's going to have
the pullback so week five we actually
did not end up taking any trades at all
we did a lot of action stuff I went to
go look at a new Penthouse that I was
looking to move into the Bugatti that I
bought my pink Bugatti we got delivery
of it with Jane juice which is another
successful student of mine from the
30-day boot camp so I bought a new car
so you yeah you don't know what car
about right you don't no all right
you're about to know in a little bit so
I was going to say something and say
some words with courage but all I have
to say is set and forget that's all I
got to say you think bro I have no words
to say honestly and it's you're the only
one that knows bro no no no I I I'm
speechless honestly I'm not going to say
anything I I I'll leave it for you guys
to see it where he has made over a quar
million dollars in trading in under 6
months he got into my first boot camp at
the beginning of the year and then later
throughout 6 months after applying
everything he learned in the strategy he
made more than A4 million dollar I find
out out I'm like dude pull it to Miami
let's do a podcast you know I like to
show traders that if they apply the
strategy and they do everything the
right way the lifestyle that they want
it's just couple moves away all you have
to do is execute the strategy correctly
so later throughout the week just more
day-to-day action in my life and we did
not take any trades so keep in mind the
week before this we ended up taking our
first loss then the week after this
which week five we ended up taking no
traits which kind of made me feel a
little bit not like Superman anymore cuz
at the beginning of the challenge I felt
Invincible now this times I'm getting a
little bit more humbled and being very
selective on the type of Trades that I'm
taking because obviously I don't want to
blow the account now I'm so ahead I have
so much time in front of me that I want
to be on track to complete the challenge
it's week six of me turning $100 into a
million and let me tell you you guys
aren't ready for this week then we
started off week six at same exact
balance the only difference now is that
we have a Bugatti in the front of the
driveway now we got
views of my [__] Bugatti so if I
don't complete this
challenge I can't afford the Bugatti so
I definitely have to complete the
challenge and stay on Route so the goal
doesn't feel right right the Bugatti's
pink I'm wearing
blue I'll be right back give me a
second more like it huh got to be on the
same Vibe as
a bro I cannot believe I [__] did
that dude
still
surreal what's the payment on one of
those my payment is
46,000 a month and then the insurance is
like 2500 so it comes out to like 48
49,000 every month so yeah we got a lot
of work to do to make that up and to
start off the week like always we do the
Sunday swings we pick the top two top
three markets for the week ahead but I
decided to go look at my track record on
the trades that I'm taking in the
account to look at the stats like what
am I doing right what am I doing wrong
so I can learn from it and double down
on what I'm doing right and F what I'm
doing wrong currently we have taken the
100 bucks to
$88,000 you guys can see that the
starting balance was 100 bucks and it
was just updated 44 minutes ago down
below over here you can currently see
our win rate is currently a 70% of the
total amount of Trades that we have
taken we taken a total seven amount of
Trades and 100% of our trades have been
short we have not taken any long
positions and our average duration is an
interesting 20 hour now this right here
is going to be a problem very soon the
commissions that we have on the account
because the bigger obviously we start
scaling on this challenge the more
slippage the more commission everything
that we're it's going to cost us to
trade so I might be switching Brokers
very very soon not entirely sure just
yet but I will be letting you guys know
if I do well I don't Market a broker I'm
just going to let you guys know if I
switch to a broker I don't plan to
Market any broker anytime soon you know
what's funny I paid $2,000 for that
lighter it doesn't work now I have to
use this $20 what is it how much I don't
even know how much is this like $5 at a
gas
station [__] sucks it just doesn't feel
right lighting a good cigar with a $5
lighter from a gas station feel like I'm
disrespecting the
cigar $2,000 on a lighter GBP CHF
probably one of the cleanest ones that
you can probably see and it is this
beautiful higher high higher low higher
high higher low higher high higher low
higher high boom shift the structure
lower low lower high low or low now this
time frame is bearish now if I just show
you guys this Market structure like this
which is realistically how you have to
look at the structure of the market not
look at the market this right here is
the structure of the market and you can
clearly see how we were creating higher
highs higher lows then we shifted we did
a ginormous and beautifully formated
double top pattern right here and now
we're coming back to retest that
neckline of the double top to then have
a reaction to the downside would have
coincidence that the neckline of the
double top happens to also be at the
weekly EMA and also happens to have a
round psychological level 1.1 to 500
which is obviously very key because now
you just have three four things that
simply make sense at this area and order
for you to be interested in the trade
what a coincidence now we also have the
daily EMA we also have daily structure
level so on and so forth so what I'm
going to be waiting for for this trade
is for price to have a break and retest
under this little double top formation
that we're potenti potentially creating
at this area here so I have an alarm
right at the bottom of it that's going
to notify me as soon as we break out of
it and this trade once it does that it's
going to have a great risk reward we can
easily get a 1 to five or even to this
structure point and then obviously we
have a smaller stop loss we get like a 1
to six 1 to six or 7 this is a great
risk reward on this trade because we are
following the trend we're trading with
the weekly time frame we're trading with
the daily time frame and once that
double top breaks we're going to be
trading with the 4our time frame so we
have three time frames are going all in
the same direction simply just enter the
trade set and forget so after we
analyzed the top markets for the week
like always on Sunday swings we then
realized there was no markets to trade
but then we got a phone call from this
guy that was like yo you want to put
your Bugatti in a music video with Kodak
Black and Trump they want to have your
the
Bugatti um in this warehouse and have
this marching Trump's marching band
behind it playing while Kodak and all
them are rapping in front of but Trump
will be there I I mean I've been part of
a couple music videos I know how this
[__] goes you
know start pull up at 3: start at 700
end at 1 in the morning you
know bro I [__] hope it's not like
that like [__] yeah I've been listening
to codak Black since I was like 15 and
who doesn't like Trump little did I know
that I was getting scammed Trump was not
pulling up and Kodak Black pulled up 20
hours late and that same night my
Bugatti broke Kodak not here yet we'll
probably be here in like 30 minutes we
gonna leave till like 3 in the morning
watch my b
wait hold on hold on hold on hold I'm
not going to lie this ship feels a
little too
[Music]
wobbly we are still here 9:00
a.m. basically a trade update and we're
still here
well after a couple
hours finally got it
up now we got to take it from this tow
truck to that tow
truck [__] this dude I don't even want
to talk about that so after we finished
all those Shenanigans like always
patience pace and most importantly
following the set and fre strategy GBP
CHF as you guys can see we're currently
up about $6,000 so we entered this trade
earlier literally probably like [__]
I don't know like an hour ago but we're
in the middle of all these Cs and the
trade is now heading into our Direction
everything's looking very well we're
actually in a lot more profit than I
expected obviously I did not account how
volatile this pair is I did not realize
that if this pair goes into a little bit
more draw down we'll blow this account
completely cuz this pair is super
volatile I actually have not entered a
trade in GP CHF in a very long time but
this trade right here if it does hit my
takeprofit it could take account up to
like $70,000 if it does make it all the
way down here and then we were up now
from the $88,000 that we were
technically down back up to the 15,000
where we were two weeks ago so now we're
picking back up staying on track and the
goal for this week was to turn the 8,000
to 16,000 or 18,000 roughly and again I
had an executive decision to make do I
close at the profit for the week or do I
set him forget what do you think I did I
[__] said and forget drum roll please
$38,000 Ching well Fair now I think this
trade is that's why I'm not even that
excited because I do think this trade
right now in London session is going to
have a pullback let me show you so I
think now this is will have a
retracement to retest this neckline of
the left head right shoulder for then
the trade to then head to the downside
currently on the daily time frame we
close very strong as a bearish and
engulfing but we could come back and
retest these daily Wicks right here so
then the trade can continue heading to
the downside now this is where a lot of
beginner Traders will probably get you
know fomo and either close out their
positions here or they can probably set
and forget the whole entire weight
currently just waiting for it to do its
thing but then when we go close the
trade we get the most ridiculous
slippage I have ever gotten in any
trading account and I said if I'm
getting slipp
at this part in the challenge so early
on I don't want to be with this broker
anymore yo we just blew the whole
[__] account no that's how you closed
the trade
bro we literally just
blew the
whole
account like we just withdraw the money
so we just draw the money from the
current broker should get into my wallet
by the end of today maybe tomorrow and
uh we're going to deposit into to a new
broker which I might be letting you guys
soon which broker it's going to be so
you guys are going to have the same
market conditions as me current broker
right now the fees were all over the
price the commissions were okay it was
more of the slippage I would literally
try and close a trade out and I get
slipped out I wouldn't get close at the
point that I wanted to so I'm going to
be switching to a new broker today
pretty much and uh we'll see where the
challenge goes from that point and this
is why I don't Market Brokers right at
the beginning of the challenge I know
you guys asked me for what broker am I
using what broker am I using I literally
got this ass a thousand times I don't
want to Market a broker that I don't
trust and I don't have any experience
with and gladly I did Market it because
[__] I close a trade at 30,000 in profit
and then it puts me at 22 the slippage
and the spread was absolutely ridiculous
I decided to withdraw my money and then
put it into a new broker that I was
going to then test out but again keep in
mind this is the exact same account that
I then just transferred the funds into a
different one and this is where we then
pretty much moved on to week number
seven where the ending bance is about
22,000 it's week seven of me turning
this $100 into a million so then on this
next week it was week seven we were
starting wor about 22,000 and then the
goal was to take 22 to then
40 touch that touch
that what you guys know about week seven
turning $100 into a million I I I
thought I had just reversed on so I was
like oh [__] currently right now we are
up
$4,000 on the trade now I'm not excited
because of these $4,000 I could give a
[__] I'm excited about the potential of
this trade that we have taken if you
have seen last week's series you saw the
loss we avoided on this position price
had the push stop then push that's what
we are anticipating for this week to
come ahead so we avoided not making any
money this week simply because we have
experience in the market now let's stick
at it now so trade update we are
currently up $4,000 on GBP CHF so if you
guys saw last night's trade update I
explained that I was looking to enter a
trade right around this area once we had
the retest to them s So currently right
now GBP CHF has a very strong double top
formation currently creating right now
very strong bearish move if this trade
hits all the way down here we [__]
sweep 1 to 11 risk to reward
meaning we will take right now we have
35 Lots right so 35 Lots means that it's
$350 per pip so we do $350 per pip times
a take profit of
$342 Pips so
$350 time
342 Pips drum roll
please
$100,000 in AEK one single position the
beauty of this is not this we're going
to get to this no matter what what is
the beauty is how much I'm actually
putting at risk so I'm only putting at
risk so we have 30 pip stop loss so if I
do
350 per pip times $30 I'm only putting
at risk 50% of the account this is key
to growth so I'm literally risking 50%
to almost 5x the account tell me that's
not a [__] great deal so as right now
we are currently just waiting for this
position to have a confirmation body
Candlestick closure in the next 27
minutes under this level of support
right here 4our Candlestick looks very
strong very bearish engulfing can then
wait for a little retest as well for
then that structure level right there
basically more of the story all we got
to do right now is set forget just looks
so lovely dude like we're finally like
making some type of decent money like
look at this and then we ran into the
same broker issue we took the 20 and
then we took it to the 40 but we ran
into even worse slippage on this other
broker that we were testing out and
again this is why I don't Market Brokers
it's my first time trading on it and I'm
taking a good trade and when I take it
the profits that I'm supposed to be
making I literally lost it because of
the slippage on the account this is the
trades from last night GBP CHF you guys
can clearly see that we closed out all
three positions at the same exact time
one of them is in profit and then the
other got split in half or whatever and
then it was in a loss so GBP CHF last
night I explained if we had a retest of
this level and then a rejection to the
downside we can very easily continue to
head down if not if we body close above
we can come back right into our area of
Interest so we body closed above and as
I'm seeing this body close above and
then I'm seeing this rejection from the
EMA but then I see this retest of this
level of support that every single time
we're above we're clearly heading up I
say oh [__] this is the area where I
want to get out because I could get
pushed right back into my entry and I
don't want to be in a loss at this point
in the challenge I'm doing so well so
decided to close my position right at
that line right there right at 1.11
1282 right at 3:00 in the morning 4: in
the morning which is like when London
session is kicking in you guys can see
down here the times and I closed out the
first position right the 20 Lots so the
20 Lots gave me $2,000 in profit now
we're we're going to do some
calculations right now because if I
enter the position up at this point
right here and then we close out the
position let's say somewhere in here
that is a total of about 23 Pips but for
argument sake let's say 20 Pips so I am
currently risking
$200 per pip so it's going to be $200
time 20 Pips I'm supposed to be up
$4,000 on that position I am up $2,000
so they ate up 50% of my profits but
that's fine you know what high fees I'll
take it whatever not a big deal but then
the other position when I go close it it
is then in a loss why did I take a loss
on the same position that I entered at
the same spot and closed at the same
spot why did it close at a loss now this
is where I get very skeptical about
these platforms because it's just so
unnecessary like like I just I just
don't get it and this is why I also
split my lot sizes because everybody
says oh why don't you just take 180 lot
it's for this very same exact reason if
I were to take 80 Lots in a position it
would literally have one full slipped
out position versus if I split the
positions in half at least I get one and
then the other ones probably have a
little bit of slippage so I I do this
because I've dealt with this ship before
and I've been dealing it for a very long
time like this at this point was very
frustrating because I just came off of a
losing week then a break even week and
now two weeks that are technically Break
Even because of the market conditions
that the broker was giving me if I'm
running into these issues with a broker
so early on into the challenge I'm
already being skeptical because imagine
the slippage and the issues that I'm
going to be running at when I'm
fluctuating hundreds of thousand doar in
profit which is realistically like 3 4
weeks away if I double the account every
single week it's week eight of me
turning $100 into a Million last week we
took two trades where one of them made
us about $2,000 and then the other we
lost a $22,000 biggest waste of time
ever and I wasn't going to let any of
this broker issue stop me living my life
I'm going to go drift my Porsche I'm
going to go hit the gym I'm going to go
do what I have to do because at the end
of the day What affected me last time
was that I was not living my normal life
now this time I decided to you know you
know what if I take a loss if I take a
win I'm going to go hit my gym I'm going
to go take my my night trades if you
know what I'm talking about and just do
what I got to do and then later on
throughout the week we got another great
opportunity in the market which is what
we analyze on Sunday swings this market
right here currently is is having a
lower high pullback and this is what
this Market structure looks like on this
pullback right we have some structure
right here and then we are now at this
resistance level if I take this same
exact Market structure move from right
here and then I simply move it to this
Market structure here with an exception
of making this a little bit higher and
aiming this a little bit higher it's the
exact same move right here but instead
of it OB OB L being here it is now right
here it's the same exact move with the
exception of bit being a little bit
higher now what is the difference that
this had this [__] the structure up here
and that this one is having it right
here let's see what happened here to see
if we can anticipate for it to happen
here cuz we're expecting for the cells
and clearly this once it did this
pattern it then went to the downside so
let's zoom in to this 30 minutes
structure on this circle time frame
right here what did we get when we were
at this pattern right here oh okay we
got a left head right shoulder okay cool
left head right shoulder retest then
sell well let's go to current price
right now holy [__] what do we have here
left head right
shoulder [__] with me [__] with me if
you want me to keep showing you guys cuz
I see this all the time and I don't
always explain it because I it's just
normal to me this is my second language
third language and I see this literally
every single day it's very very normal
to me but to a lot of you guys this
might be like what the [__] a wild
moment and if it is let me know in the
comments so I can keep doing this stuff
for you guys cuz it motivates me and it
shows me that you guys are actually
learning so this position we're actually
very very very interested in executing
but not just yet I want to execute this
position once we have some type of
engulfing confirmation as of right now I
have my potential entry right under this
level because when this Candlestick
closes under it it is a engulfing
Candlestick so just put my alarm under
there to pretty much notify me once we
have that engulfing Candlestick even the
15minute hasn't had the engulfing quite
just yet so we're going to stay up all
night tonight because that literally
might happen very very very soon we
actually ended up taking then the
account from the 22 to about 60k in
profit more or less drum roll
please what [__] trade update
$19,000 [__] dollars in profit now
what how fast did this happen very fast
let me show you guys so right now USD
JPY exactly how I explained yesterday we
literally explained the only way we'd be
interested in taking this position right
here is if we have a break retest and
then sell price literally broke retested
sell exactly what we anticipated perfect
entry signal literally 1 hour ago as you
guys can see down here 8:00 in the
morning currently right now it is 10:00
in the morning so as soon as we entered
this position Market immediately started
heading to the downside look how fast
this momentum of this Market is
currently moving beautiful 30 minutes
bearish engulfing Evening Star formation
15minute time frame at soon as the
Candlestick close boom just completely
downside move which is absolutely
beautiful this is the trade that we
avoided yesterday and we avoided to take
the loss cuz it never retested and gave
us the engulfing of this this left head
and the right shoulder now avoided this
loss we can remove this now we have this
position right here we're just looking
decent right obviously I'm just hyped
because I risked a lot more than I
should have because we're trying to turn
$20,000 into 40 so I can literally close
the position right now and then we will
have the $40,000 in profit that we need
literally oh oh [__] oh oh oh what oh
[__] what the [__] just happened oh [__]
oh oh
whoo whoo whoo whoo whoo whoo whoa wo wo
W whoo whoo
wo don't you [__] do
it hold on I'm in the I'm in shock right
now yo I saw 50,000 it was it was at the
bottom of that Wick right there is news
happening right now probably well now
I'm on edge I'm going to put an alarm
right around my entry signal just to let
me know that it is up there I have to
put a an alarm at the bottom of this
Candlestick if we if we get a
Candlestick to go back under that Wick
we're pretty much good we are
good okay time to foret you you don't
want
this all right so currently right now we
had a little quick uh spazz in the
markets this is what trading in the
market is this is why people go crazy
when they risk more money than they
should if I was risking you know 3 4 5%
like a normal human I would even care
oh right now $40,000 floting and profit
that's it I'll be care
about oh [__] oh [__] oh [__] oh [__] yo
oh [__] yo no yo yo I yo I can't make
this up dude yo I can't make this up
dude holy holy [__] holy [__] bro yo
stoping dude oh oh yo 100,000 yo there's
no
way yo there's no
way yo yo there's no there's no way oh I
kind of hurt
myself is my watch okay yeah it's fine
doesn't matter we can buy another one oh
oh oh dude oh yo we're about to be at
100,000 that's [__]
crazy yo the countdown is
legendary
yo no no no no we got to keep going we
got to keep
going got to keep going we got to keep
going
95 95 oh 97 yo it's going to hit 100,000
yo it's going to hit 100,000 we got to
keep going look dude I think I think we
got it to
like dude do we got up to
[Music]
there now now I just got to
focus what is it on
I didn't do
this this right here shows you guys that
the
[__] fundamentals will follow the
technicals all right I got to focus dude
market update boys market update boys
and ladies and gentlemen we have
officially officially closed the
accounts at no no no drum roll please
thank you very much we have officially
closed at 90,000
[__] dollars on the account so we
ended off the week I think about 90,000
80,000 something like that in profit and
honestly I didn't have really anything
else to do so I had a bright idea why
not buy five six junk cars call my other
rich friends and let's just go play
bumper cars
[Music]
[__] so we ended off closing off the
week with about 90,000 I think in profit
and playing bumper cards which is pretty
legendary because I got a pretty big
group of people
together in under two hours like imagine
you getting a phone call saying yo pull
up to this location and let's play
bumper cars everybody's reaction is like
what the [__] good morning ladies and
gentlemen as much as I would want to go
right into the markets and show you my
trades on this week where I'm going to
be tearing the $990,000
200 I have to spoon feed my children my
very special unique children that haters
come here come here airplane
so the beginning of week nine something
that I expected to happen happened the
haters the haters decided to arise and
they decided to then voice their
opinions on their challenge now keep in
mind haters were not voicing their
opinion up to this point why because the
account wasn't big enough turning 100 to
300 and then 300 to 4 5,000 is just not
exciting but now when I started having
multiple six figures fluctuating
automatically people wanted to then say
he's not showing the trade history it's
not real he blew the account like if I
have not been showing every single trade
the before the during the after up to
this point literally showing every
single trade in my free Telegram in my
Discord in my Instagram on YouTube they
wanted to voice their opinions and I
said okay you know what nobody's going
to [__] with my reputation my
reputation's everything so I addressed
the haters showed the trade history and
then continue on with the journey
because truthfully if they were
concerned about the challenge being
legit at this point I said you know what
thank you that means I'm not doing good
of enough a job let me double down on
making this even more transparent and
even more legit ladies and gentlemen it
is currently
11:15 in the morning and as of right now
the account is currently sitting at a
whopping you blew the account psych
$15,000 now you know what let me just
we're currently sitting at
$115,000 now the reason why I'm not
excited is because we could have
literally been in this much profit we've
been holding the last trade but sucks so
we have to overexpose ourselves but it's
okay why because the strategy is working
once again nzdcad literally having left
head right shoulder retest of the
neckline exactly what I explained sh on
the 1 hour time frame higher high higher
low higher high once it breaks and
retests this neckline we will be
interested in selling and boys that is
exactly what we did we broke and we
retested once again like does not get
any more legit than this oh but you want
to know what's the crazy part that the
downside potential of this trade is
massive we can reach lows of all the way
up to this structure point right here
but we're not going to do that we're not
going to be greedy we're going to be
real second set real take profits and we
entered this position once we body Clos
under this right here we're pretty much
good and very ironically the same week
that I call out the haters is the same
week where I'm supposed to be
fluctuating in multiple six figures and
profits actually ended up having the
biggest loss I don't even know why I'm
laughing at this point we blew the
account boys to
44,000 [__] bro this is why we can't
[__] around talking [__] we [__]
jinxed it talking [__] so we just
took a unnecessarily $40,000 loss on ndd
CAD the same week I decided to troll the
haters which honestly it was kind of
funny because I made it even more legit
even more transparent and I expected to
win a trade and I lost I lost in front
of everybody and after I trolled the
haters which kind of like a it was an L
on my side but you know what I'm glad
I'm glad that that happened because that
only Made Me Stronger to then come into
the next week so we started off the
challenge this week on about 990,000 and
we ended off on 40 which kind of sucks
because after you address haters you
want to win you want to win on the
haters I lost on the haters even though
we did lose 50% of the account I did
something the haters can't I got on a G4
to go to Dominican Republic to not only
do a podcast on the jet but to go check
out my tobacco farm that I have for this
brand that I'm actually building which
is my new cigar brand and I said okay I
might have lost for the week but let's
take this private jet this cool podcast
and be back in about 36 hours just to
check up on how the cigars are doing and
coming right back so the haters had to
laugh at the beginning of the week but
then I had it at the end of the week all
right ladies and gentlemen good morning
let's head to our office let me show you
the starting balance for this week on
the account wrong
phone right phone so right now the
starting balance for this week is going
to be
$444,000 so to start off week 10 we got
on the Jet right back to Miami but
before I leave I like taking care of the
people that took care of me while we're
out in this trip in Dominican Republic
had one of the best chefs one of the
best Services T them about $2 $3,000 in
ones that I happened to find in my
duffel bag don't ask me why it's ones
don't ask me how it got there I don't
know
[Applause]
you know what's funny you give like you
can give somebody in the United States
$10,000 like cash like a big stack like
this and they'll be like thanks like
they won they won't give a [__] first
thing that I do when I get back is put
up the time piece trading buy a new
Richard Mill cuz I felt like my wrist
was a little weak you know I'm like you
know what we've been doing this for 10
weeks I need some motivation I need
something better Bugatti is not enough
and it's broken let's go buy a new Rich
M so what you just picked up it's
limited to 50 pieces in the world it's
the Asia Edition it's carbon super light
I think it's cool like it's good
contrast from your like your white watch
your gold watch you know what makes this
like the Asia Edition the the color way
oh like the black and black gold bro I
like this one I think I'm going take
this one that's
it easy to sell to this guy
Bro [__] it why not we bought a chain
for Ste would do it we gave give away
out to him cuz you're always giving back
you know
what the [__] going
on a good back you know he never gets
gifts so I was like let me be the first
guy to actually gift this guy something
he's always giving other people stuff
and I thought it was a nice gesture he
doesn't need it probably got the chain
throws it into a safe and never licks at
it ever again but my conscious it's good
we are currently in a position that we
are going to continue to set and
forget I mean I literally just called it
last night it's not my first time
calling it all right boys so market
update we are currently up
41,000 so we're back at we're not even
back where we were last week and we just
did the dumbest thing ever we just
executed a loss right here because we
decided to enter this position right
around this area thinking that it was
just going to continue to go down like
when you don't sleep all night you just
start seeing [__] but then I go down to
the 1 hour I'm like but wait this price
definitely has the opportunity to come
back and retest this level of support
and resistance just how it did here it
could even go up further it could
literally go back up all the way up to
this area right around here before
actually going
down so the 80 lot that I took at that
point right there I simply closed it cuz
it was actually [__] so now I
currently in this position um literally
what I said yesterday we're ready to
execute it we're just waiting for the
right confirmations we just got the
break of the structure how I wanted to
enter the
EMA and yeah we're in this position now
so I'm just going to anticipate for
price to continue having a push to the
downside after this retest uh we avoided
a loss yesterday on Euro GBP avoided a
loss on GBP JPY and avoided a loss on
Euro AUD so we've been dodging bullets
all week finally managed to catch one
that allign with the strategy we closed
the position at the top of this Wick up
here and literally we probably did the
best decision we could have done we
closed these two positions at a $2,000
loss for a total of 160 Lots then we
waited for price to have its rejection
now some of you guys would have been
like wow you closed for no reason you
could have still been holding the trade
you know what you're right you're right
dude but you wouldn't be up $63,000 if I
did not do that why because I waited for
this next entry bearish engulfing
confirmation uh Evening Star formation
under the EMA rejection from the
structure and I said you know what okay
fine you want to take me out of break
even and you want to make me lose an
extra 15 Pips from the original entry
that I originally had up here from this
to this point okay fine I'll make it
back by risking
170 more Lots on this position before we
had 160 Lots which was these positions
right here 80 plus 80 is 160 you add all
these up and we have 330 so we
essentially almost doubled a little bit
over the risk that we had before but we
got an extra confirmation that we did
not get here and you know what I [__]
with it because yeah we lose 15 pits
from the entry but we gain 170 Lots it
sucks on the short term but on the long
term trust me it's going to pay
off man dude how stressful dude these
last couple of hours
yes yes in profit like we weren't just
up $70,000 [__] dollar this shit's
making me go crazy all right we just got
out right now at
[__] I don't know dude I don't even
know how much that is um like $6,000 in
profit 5,000
whatever bro what a swing dude how do
you go from like 13 how do you go from
$70,000 in profit to then $113,000
drw down to now only making 4 grand tell
me how that works so we ended off week
10 pretty choppy kind of whack can't
even lie because we spend a lot of money
but we didn't make a lot of money but
then come week 11 we do the same thing
pick the top pairs for the week but now
this time we did a major comeback
welcome to week 11 trainning $100 into a
million we made up for the slack that we
did in 2 weeks because we took the
account balance from what we were
starting at to about
$200,000 now you might be wondering what
the [__] the video just started it
didn't the video started yesterday on
Sunday swings welcome welcome welcome to
another Sunday swings where I literally
broke down every single one of these
trades to the te I entered USD CAD on
the sales once again so if you guys go
watch last week's series you guys would
see what I went through last week right
here at this very moment I entered this
trade got stopped out at break even I
closed out of Break Even I entered this
trade closed myself out of break even
right here it was an absolute brutal
Friday now price came back into the area
did exactly what I said it was going to
do and then we executed the positions
right at the top of this area such a
beautiful trade look at this retest here
from this level of support support
support resistance rejection from the
EMA daily time frame currently having
that re break of structure this daily
Candlestick and golf 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9
10 11 candlesticks then we had the
pullback then we had the weekly double
dogee rejection from the EMA rejection
from the structure like there's so many
things that are going to make this trade
create a new lower low rather than
create a higher high all I did was
simply re-enter the trade where I was
originally entered the only thing that
changed is the mindset behind when I
enter this trade versus when I entered
this trade but if you notice I'm taking
the the exact same tra look at the
pattern formation here and where it is
it's at the area of Interest EMA look at
the pattern formation here it's at the
area of interest and EMA and then you
simply set and forgets and we are now up
$168,000 and yes it's the same account
as always boys you guys can see right
here in the trade history we could like
I can literally close this position
right now so it's literally Monday
morning and I can literally close out
this position at this very point right
here and be done for the week and there
goes this series 10 5 minutes but you
know what we're not stopping there we're
going to keep it going we're going to
try and turn this 100 something thousand
into the million today now the goal for
the week was to double the account and
like always I see the structure
continuing with the trend so I'm going
to set and forget I want to maximize my
profits but minimize my losses trade
update it is currently
12:45 in the morning it's about to be
1:00 a.m. right now we are in a new
position where now the account is up 35
gazillion dollars I'm kidding we're
still at the same exact spot still no
trades that we have added on to the
challenge so we did miss this new added
position on USD CAD as you guys can see
pric has actually had a retracement to
the area exactly how I anticipated price
came back ret the structure level and
now it looks like it's having a sell
down we literally pulled out right I
mean you know we had a little bit more
that we could have potentially gotten
but you know it's simply not worth it so
we got out at the perfect area right
before this retracement we're looking to
add positions here but the session was
not the right session to be entering
this trade so for me to be interested in
adding a new position I would have to
wait for a retest here to then head to
the downside so I'm going to be waiting
for that lower high to then sell wake up
the next day and I see the trade could
have tripled the account I could have
closed the account at half a million
dollar by doing nothing and you know
this did mess with my psychology a
little bit but I'm leading by example I
have too many people watching me I have
to be realistic and be like you know
what guys this is going to happen you're
going to set and forget and you're going
to close at the point where you thought
it was the final point before price
reversed but the trade keeps on going
it's okay you made money you H your take
profit you move on so I did miss out on
about 300K on the trade but it's okay
because I hit the profit for the week
and we showed people that we can come
back from two losing weeks two break
evening weeks to now triple the account
on one single
trade it's week 12 of me turning this
into a million day trading so on week 12
is where things start getting a little
interesting because now every single
trade we're about to take is going to
fluctuate hundreds of thousands of
dollars so like always the pairs that we
analyze on Sunday swings ended up taking
it we fluctuated up and down trade
update I feel like I I feel like I've
said this a million times trade update
right now we are up5 $9,000 on the
account but not only have I said this a
million times I'm talking about this oh
oh oh oh oh yo what is going on every
single time yo what the [__] yo it's
every time dude yo I can't make this up
dude yo I can't make this [__] up bro I
can't make this
up bro I was literally going to say we
have the head and shoulders pattern we
see this pattern a gazillion times and
then we usually always have the retest
to then sell dude what is happening dude
what is happening
bro all right well look at that there
goes our trade update right there we're
up 100,000 they go for the week is half
a ticket bro what's there come on do
your thing and dude I was just so calm I
was so relaxed I was so
Pacific well the goal was to show you
guys that what I said we needed
yesterday to happen which was The Head
and Shoulders we put our alarm at the
shift of structure and once we body
close under it we get the retest and
then we sell that's basically it we'
we've said it a 100 [__]
times you can't make this up dude you
can not make this up okay so right now
we are up exactly a 1 to 1 and we're up
about
100,000 that means when we get to a 1 to
two we we should be up 200,000 and when
we get to a 1 the three we'll be up
300,000 isn't that beautiful don't you
want to have your easy math like that
every single time you add a risk for
reward it's just an extra 100K 100K 100K
sounds good to me this is why I didn't
want to celebrate earlier or be anywhere
near excited because I expected for
something like this to happen we are
currently down about
$225,000 in the account when we were up
earlier about 150,000 at that height of
it the markets didy did the did out of
me look at this price went not only
straight into our stop loss but a
complete violation break through the
previous structure level almost through
the screen and out the [__] roof we
just got Diddy DD in the
didd is that even real [__] luckily we
did not risk much on the position we are
only back at
$135,000 and we only took about a
$68,000 loss on the account which given
this trade I should have risked 100% but
I explain to you the higher I go in the
account I lower my Risk by 25 to 50% so
I'm not even mad I I I'm not it's just
it's one of those losses with this type
of approach you know Albert Einstein has
projects that sometimes don't don't do
well and right now we are not doing well
we're still at the same exact spot still
no new positions into the account so our
trade ideas are going to potentially
start moving as of right now GBP CHF for
CS I love how this price action is
currently looking right now daily time
frame close with a daily dogee and if we
go down to the 1 Hour 1 hour has had
what looks to be like a little double
top I'm literally going to wait for a
break and retest under this area right
here so this is kind of like the
consolidation Zone it's in so I want to
have some type of break out of this and
then a quick retest to then sell a
little break out then a quick retest to
then sell everything depends on the
price action but I want to enter here
but I can't enter here right now I need
to breakout confirmation and then the
pull back to enter here I don't mind
entering a little bit lower but I just
need the confirmation that it's having a
break on it's having a move we are up
200 and
38,000 [__] dollars GBP C F
trade update so right now we have three
very unique entries on GBP CHF and I
want to explain them to Perfection
because this moved very fast literally
only like 4 hours this is just one
Candlestick so GBP CHF we had the 4-Hour
bearish engulfing how I wanted from that
area and then we obviously entered at
the breakout of all of this
consolidation Zone here I entered on
this 1 in the morning Candlestick as it
was getting ready to close entered right
there spread took me a little bit down
and then we add our next entry on this
15minute pullback so we had the full
move I'm like yes amazing beautiful but
then we had this pullback and on this
pullback I waited for this engulfing
confirmation we entered on this pullback
of this Wick and then the next entry we
entered at the bottom of that rejection
candle right there and those are our
three entries we have our first one up
here our second right here and our third
one right around here and our take
profit was very strategically placed at
this next 4our low so as you can see the
4 Hour is clearly bearish higher high
higher low D bearish lower low lower
high lower low lower high we're destined
to create a new lower low but up to
where up to this structure point and you
can clearly see that price has very well
reacted from that structure point this
is only a 1 to 2.7 risk reward and we've
risked a lot more than what we're
risking here on different markets this
move just happens to be very very
volatile like we're up 102 Pips right
now we got a sudden and forget the trade
either hits my stop loss or hits my
takeprofit and I sudden and forget and
the trade ended up closing off at the
highest point which I think it was about
$400,000 at this point where the
challenge is right now so we stuck to
our trading plan we held oursel
accountable while doing this live in
front of hundreds of thousands of people
on my telegram Discord Instagram YouTube
absolutely everywhere I'm not the only
one making money at this point there's
so many of you guys that have done your
own flips that I'm like oh [__] this
shit's getting serious I did a podcast
with a student that by copying my exact
same trades he took uh what was it I
think he took $1,000 to
$150,000 this guy by just watching my
Instagram stories became a six figure
person by watching 10sec Instagram
stories talk about [__] value trade
update we closed at 332,000
trade history as you guys can see we
have officially closed the position at
the highest point keyw we've closed the
position we were just up 400,000 we lost
70k just because of [__] floating
[__]
out well you know what we actually want
to trade we shouldn't be doing that so
after we closed off on week 12 at about
$400,000 on week 13 I got a bright idea
we're gonna [__] live stream the last
trade turning 400 into a million [__] it
I came up with a bright idea to do it on
Instagram I go on Instagram try to do an
IG live doesn't let me said okay you
know what everything happens for a
reason let's then go to YouTube and we
start a live stream turning $400,000 to
$800,000 all right ladies and gentlemen
welcome to the live stream today in the
morning when I I literally just woke up
like an hour ago and I'm seeing the
trade that I took last night I'm like yo
I have to do an IG live from the moment
that I wake up till this trade hits a
million then I go to my Ig so I'm going
to show you guys right now so this is my
account as you guys can see when I go
into my account I go into my settings
and I'm trying to go on live so I'm I'm
going to do it right now with you guys
right so right here on my Ig I try and
go live so I click here
live at this time here accounts is not
eligible to use this so even if I wanted
to I couldn't go live on Instagram and
I'm like [__] how do I stream like for
me this very point the whole entire way
of me turning the 100 to the amount like
it's going to literally be like the
rawest day in the life that I think
anybody has ever done so basically we're
going to stream until this account turns
into a MK whether it happens today
tomorrow the day after I don't plan to
turn off the stream until we don't reach
the million so this can last an hour
which I don't think so based off of the
price action or this can last 24 hours
this can last 48 hours I will not shut
off this stream until we don't complete
the challenge this is something that is
legendary and that I want it to be
documented the whole entire way so get
prepared get comfortable cuz this is
going to be an
interesting 24hours 48 Hours you guys
are going to see real day in my life
obviously like if I had to enter some
meetings and stuff you know I can't have
you guys be part of that I just kind of
like put it to the phone and [__]
so I mean s we're we're live bro like
what do we do now like we're just live
look this is literally live right
now Focus how much are we up 600
[__] yeah there you there you
go history hold up is it focusing
is it focusing yeah put a little
higher yeah there you go you want it
higher than that huh okay so basically
we have USD CHF where basically we have
been interested in taking this position
since early this week you guys can tell
how we've had this very strong
consolidation Zone and then what we
ended up doing is we broke out of that
consolidation Zone let me actually take
off all these writings so once we broke
out of this consolidation Zone we were
then waiting for price to have a retest
of this area once it retested this
structure then we would continue to head
to the upside now this had the retest
exactly not exactly as I wanted to but
it made it to the area and we had the
most important thing which is going to
be our entry signal which is this right
here this right here is our entry signal
not this specifically but there's
something in here that happened that is
my entry signal and I don't really ever
speak about it and you know what I'm
going to talk about it on the stream but
not right now cuz we just got started
with the stream and I don't see this
Market moving for the
next 7 hours so only to the soldiers
that are with me for these next seven
hours that I'm doing this stream am I
going to actually break everything down
of my strategy and everything
so I I I you know I feel like I came up
with this idea and I haven't really
processed that we didn't really put some
bro for real dude what the [__] bro cuz
now I can't turn it
off I just can't I'm so committed I I
can't I live stream for literally 26
hours I was with you guys when I went to
throw away trash when I went to go eat
when I went to go drift when I went to
go do my day-to-day life I literally was
with you guys all the time so I did want
to say this is probably one of the most
spontaneous little events I've done I
probably expected five people to pull up
six people to up we have well over
almost like 50 60 people it's 2:00 in
the morning you guys are Maniacs right
I'm telling you guys know I thought I
was a freak staying up all night
watching the markets are well clear I'm
the only one I could be a maniac I could
be a maniac but I'm not the only one I'm
surrounded by other people that are
passionate about this [__] people that
are willing to do whatever the [__] it
takes to make this [__] go down and like
yeah it's cool that I you know dropped
the pin and was able to get you guys
here together but like this [__] is not
about me bro like this this is about you
guys you guys got to realize that you
guys are doing the same thing that I'm
doing to be able to be on the same
Journey that I am you guys are staying
up you guys are putting money at risk
you guys are learning failing rinse and
repeating and over time you're not the
same person that you were last month
compared to now so I just want to say
like the people that you are around
right now are the people you want to be
around with you're the fifth person out
of the four people in your friend group
if your four friends are smoking weed
you're [__] smoking weed if your four
friends are Diddy you're the fit Diddy
how it go you guys were telling me to
close the trade when we were up 700,000
this is not done there's a lot more in
this you guys told me to close the trade
when price started pulling back and we
were at 600,000 and on the live stream
not only am I answering all your guys'
questions but I am literally engraving
the mindset you need to adapt to be able
to handle these types of swings the
trade isn't done if the trade is not hit
the take profit you do not close the
trade was at about 700,000 and I wish
you could see the chat literally
thousands of people live watching saying
close close close close clearly none of
these people are my students and they
don't know how the set and forget
strategy works the set and forget
strategy works by set and forgetting you
have a stop- loss you have a take profit
price is either going to hit one or the
other and guess what we did we set him
[__] forget we have officially closed
the challenge
800,000 just do it the trade not only
hit our takeprofit and we close at
800,000 the trade continued to create
new highs if I would have just continued
to hold for two more hours I would have
completely finished the challenge at
this very moment I could have finished
it on a legendary 26-hour stream but you
know what I'm glad that I followed my
strategy and I closed at where I did
because then this gave me the
opportunity on week 14 to start off a
stream right at the beginning of the
week where then we took the final
$800,000
to then the
million and all I can say you know what
I'm going to let the stream speak for
itself and you know what I think my
celebration was a little extra I can't
even lie but how would you feel after
you turned the $100 into a million I
think you'll be
excited right now my
yeah and on both streams I'm talking
about stream one where we stream for 26
hours and on stream to on week 14 I was
letting everybody know that once I
completed the challenge I wasn't just
going to stop there I knew that once I
would complete the challenge I was going
to be bored because achieving the
challenge is cool it's showing people
that it could be done but it doesn't
show you guys the how so I came up with
the bright idea that if I complete this
100 to the mill series I am going to
open a 30-day boot camp I'm going to
open 300 new spots to take on Traders
literally from Level zero to 100 to
replicate the exact same thing that I
did where I'm going to teach my most
lated and updated version of my strategy
on how exactly I turned 100 to the maill
I can teach anybody I'm talking about
your grandma that doesn't know anything
about trading to an experience Trader
that is having some type of profits but
not the type that he wants get him from
literally level 0 to 100 to trade just
like me and have the same results as me
so this is where I came up with the
30-day boot camp and it's literally my
third time doing this and the results of
the students that are part of this boot
camp are literally unheard of students
that have literally known nothing from
trading in their first six months they
make their first payout and even first
six figures you can take Jay and juice
for example you can take Mike where Mike
took $1,000 in his first four months of
trading after the boot camp he turned it
into
$120,000 so this 30-day boot camp is now
going to be your journey of the 100 to
the mail I'm going to literally show
these 300 new students that I personally
can select how to replicate exactly what
I did I'm going to take you from Level
zero to 100 and even if let's say you're
at level 70 or if you think you are I
have to reteach you how to read I have
to retach you how to read the markets so
you can read them exactly how I do and
you can apply the exact strategy on how
I do it and this is the beauty of the
set and for guet strategy it is so
simple to learn and have results that
I've had hundreds of students all around
the world have results just like mine
not only by copying and being part of my
journey but then finding their own
markets and them being able to do it for
themselves which honestly it's the best
feeling ever so the hundreds of the mil
challenge was completed but it doesn't
end there now Begins the next challenge
the 30-day boot camp boot camp is
literally ridiculous but truthfully I
can't teach everybody that wants to be
part of the 30-day boot camp I have to
limit it to a certain amount of Traders
because I want to give quality to the
people that deserve it so if you want to
be part of this 30-day boot camp you
have to apply there's no way of you
joining if you do not apply to the
30-day boot camp I want to review your
application the effort and the time that
you put into your application is the
same exact time and effort that I'm
going to put into reviewing your
application and deciding if I'm going to
accept these new students or not because
truthfully this is my second mic drop in
the industry the first one is I
completed the challenge big mic drop did
it live on a stream with absolutely
everybody watching the before during the
after of every single trade but now it's
my time to put time into you guys the
100 to the mail I did it for myself and
my own game yes I turned the 100 into
the mail cool but that doesn't really do
anything for you guys you guys don't
really capitalize off of it unless you
were copying all the trades and Me part
of the journey those you guys that
couldn't because of work because of your
time because you just weren't able to
tune in every single day to the trades i
s in my telegram Instagram YouTube this
is what this 30-day boot camp is for so
you can learn the strategy and you be
able to implement it yourself and you
have your own journey and make trading
your new source of income in this
upcoming year so if you want to be part
of this 30-day boot camp and have the
same exact results as students like J
and juice or Mike make sure you apply to
the 30-day boot camp I'm going to review
your application and decide if you get
accepted or not because truthfully I'm
ready to now take on this new challenge
and have the second biggest mic drop in
the industry by taking the biggest
amount of traders that I personally can
manage to take them from Level zero to
100 and make trading their new source of
income in this upcoming year so
truthfully all I can say is whenever in
doubt set and forget thank you guys for
watching the whole entire 100 to the
mill series I'm very very very very
proud of all of you guys that stayed
tuned throughout the whole entire
Journey everything that you guys learned
thank you guys for supporting and being
there with me for this journey but this
chapter has now ended and I have just
opened a new one with these 300 new
students I'll see the 300 new students
on the 30-day boot camp when we begin
you guys want to be part of it make sure
you guys apply below and all I can say
is I and forget